Okay, so let's take this a step further.
How would we access an object inside of
an array? Um, well, let's go back to our
syntax. How do we access something
inside of an array? Well, we would say
my array at the zero position. Great.
How would we access something inside of
an object? Well, we'd say my object dot
and then the name that we're trying to
access.
So, how would I print out Tim Drake?
Well, I would say console.log. And then
let's look at our syntax.
The object is inside of the array. How
do we access something in array? Well,
I've shown you that syntax here. So,
we'd say my array the zero position.
What is in the zero position of the
array? Well, it's an object. How do we
access something in an object? Well,
there's two ways. We could either say
name. So, we're saying go into the zero
position of the array, which is this,
and grab the name attribute,
which is this. Or the other way I could
do this is I say go into my array at the
zero position name. And in that way I
would be able to print out Tim Drake.
And that concludes this video on
accessing an object inside of an array.